A cop who enforces his own brand of justice.
Stone Cold is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Craig R. Baxley.
Joe Huff is a tough, loner cop with a flair for
infiltrating dangerous biker gangs.
The FBI blackmail Huff into an undercover operation that entails infiltrating The Brotherhood – a powerful
Mississippi biker gang linked in the murder of government officials as well as dealing drugs with the mafia.
Joe Huff / John Stone, played by Brian Bosworth.
Chains Cooper, played by Lance Henriksen.
Ice, played by William Forsythe.
Nancy, played by Arabella Holzbog.
Lance, played by Sam McMurray.
Cunningham, played by Richard Gant.
Stone Cold is a 1991 action film directed by Craig R.
Baxley, starring American football star Brian Bosworth in his acting debut.
The film's story centers on a biker gang that tries to assassinate the district
attorney and free one of their members who is on his trial for the murder.
The film performed poorly at the box office, grossing
$9 million on its $25 million budget.
The film explores themes of undercover, fbi, biker, cop, motorcycle gang.
The tone is emotional and intense.